Nilam

Address: Pehowa, Haryana, India Pincode: 136030 Contact: 9671261811 anumohre1234@gmail.com

SUMMARY

A dedicated and result-oriented Software Engineer with approximately **one year of experience**. Can work well under pressure and make the best of any situation. Best grip in **Core Java, Advanced Java, REST API React.js** and **JavaScript.**

CORE COMPETENCIES

• Core Java

• Collection Framework

JDBC

Servlet

• Data Structure

DBMS

Algorithms

JavaScript

Spring boot

• React JS

Docker

SKILLS

• Languages: Java, C, C++, SQL, JavaScript

• Frameworks: J2EE ,Hibernate ,Spring, Spring boot

API's: Servlets , REST, Stream
Software: Eclipse, Postman
Databases: MySQL, Oracle

• Tools: Docker

EXPERIENCE

AXYYA DIGITAL

System Engineer

May 2022- Present

- Completed training on Java frameworks like Hibernate, Spring, Spring boot and Microservices
- Completed training on deployment tools like Docker and Kubernetes.
- Completed training on React JS Library.

Jai Sustainability Solutions & Co.

Software Developer

Gurgaon, Haryana August 2021 – May 2022

- Worked on Energy Management System project.
- During experience Java is the main technology used for backend .
- JavaScript used for making the interactive UI.

EARLY CAREER EXPERIENCE

S.O. Infotech Pvt Ltd

Noida, UP

Intern

June 2019 – August 2019

- During internship I worked on Core Java and Collection Framework.
- Worked on Banking Domain project which developed on Java.
- Frontend Developed on HTML and CSS and Backend Developed on Java and JDBC.

Energy Management System Software Developer

Gurgaon, Haryana August 2021 – May 2022

- Project developed on Core Java, JSON, JavaScript.
- Worked on Full Stack Development.
- In Backend I developed modules on Core Java.
- Frontend I Designed Web page on HTML, JavaScript.

EDUCATION

JMI Engineering & Technical Institute BTech (CSE) Graduation with 76%

Radaur, Haryana June 2021

Jai Ram Public School
Senior Secondary Certificate (CBSE) with 75%

Kurukshetra, Haryana June 2016

Geeta S D Public schoolMatriculation (HBSE) with 75%

Kaithal, Haryana June 2014